(Amy:)I'm regretting
my earlier cattiness.
(Amy:)She is an
absolute delight.
(Leonard:)Wow.
(Howard:)Wow, indeed.
(Bernadette:)I can't believe we're
finally living together.
(Howard:)Yeah.
(Howard:)You know what would make
this moment perfect?
(Bernadette:)What?
(Howard:)A little snack.
You got any string cheese?
(Bernadette:)No.
I-I might have some cheddar.
(Howard:)Not as good.
(Howard:)You can't make strings with it.
(Howard:)Remind me to put it
on your shopping list.
(Howard:)Okay.
(Howard:)You have
hypo-allergenic detergent?
(Bernadette:)No.
(Howard:)Better put it on the list.
(Howard:)If you wash my underwear
with regular soap,
I get little red bumps
on my tuchus.
(Bernadette:)Wait a second.
(Bernadette:)I'm doing your laundry?
(Howard:)Well, honey,
it's not gonna do itself.